# **CHRISTINA BARRON**

2430 Nielsen St., El Cajon 92020

+916-201-9552 barron.i.christina@gmail.com

### PROFILE

Dedicated Customer Service Representative with over 10 years of experience providing solutions for a diverse range of needs, from handling calls and in-person requests from the community as receptionist at a mega-church, to working with owners and entrepreneurs designing websites and graphics to meet their specific business objectives.

## PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Design Time Management MS Word, Excel, Quickbooks Adaptivity

## EDUCATION

BA in Business Administration: Integrated Marketing with an emphasis in Communication San Diego State University | 2006 - 2010

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Website and Graphic Designer

2021 - PRESENT

Christina Barron Designs | La Mesa

- Creates and manages websites for a variety of clients including non-profits and small businesses
- Designs graphics and logos for client's businesses and events in Canva, Illustrator and Photoshop

## **Customer Service Representative**

2020 - 2021

LightStream | San Diego

- · Responsible for responding to general account questions from clients, via phone and email, often involving sensitive or private information (financial statements, Covid-19 concerns, etc.)
- Addressed and resolved customer problems and complaints by clarifying the issue, explaining the best solution, and following up with clients

## **Administrative and Social Media Coordinator**

2011 - 2020

Journey Community Church | La Mesa

- Provided in-person and over the phone community support (food, clothing, counseling, connecting to resources) to ~75 people/week
- Managed weekly updates and requests for support from congregants (average of 2,000 each week) for pastoral care and community outreach teams
- Managed social media for accounts with 1400-3800 unique followers; including writing and editing daily posts, and managing engagement on all posts
- Designed graphics for classes, meetings, events, and community outreach